Kochan, Thomas A. Kaiser Permanente Research Materials for "Healing Together" 6251
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Thomas A. Kochan Kaiser Permanente Research Materials for "Healing Together"
2004-2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kochan, Thomas A.
6251
5 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records.
8259723
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 22, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6251 AV: Thomas A. Kochan Kaiser Permanente Research Materials Audio-Visual Materials 6262: Thomas A. Kochan Collection of Dunlop Commission Papers
Kochan, Thomas A.
8259723
- BTG Reports to the CIC June 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cleveland (Box 1, Folder 2)
- MIT Global Airline Industry Program, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 2005 Guiding Principles (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Promotional Material (Box 1, Folder 5)
- MIT Sloan Packets (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Your Guide to Common Issues in Bargaining, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Kansas (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 2005 Negotiations and Bargaining (1 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 2005 Negotiations and Bargaining (2 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 2005 Negotiations and Bargaining (3 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 2005 Negotiations and Bargaining (4 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 2005 Negotiations and Bargaining (5 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 2006 Bargaining and Negotiations (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Think Outside the Box (pin) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Time Account (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Current ICP (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Healing Together: The Labor Management Partnership at Kaiser Permanente (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Negotiations: 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- N/SA (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Case Study, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 2007 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 2009 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 13)
- KP and CKPU (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Regional LMP Co-Chairs National Meeting (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Kaiser Permanente & AFL-CIO Labor Management Partnership, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kaiser Metrics (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Harvard/MIT Resource Binder (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Kaiser Permanente Project: Interviews and Notes (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Partnership Orientation (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Leaders' Guide: Interest Based Problem Solving (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Summary: Ohio K-P Labor Management Partnership (Box 3, Folder 9)
- A Briefing for the Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations (Box 3, Folder 10)
- National Agreement Reopener Bargaining (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lovell Committee (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Lovell Committee Meeting 9/18/87, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Lovell Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- National Policy Association (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Lovell Committee (Box 4, Folder 5)
- NPA/ Collective Bargaining (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Work Outside the Box (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Labor Management Partnership: Workplace Safety Initiative (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Improving the PSP in 2009-2010 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Participant's Notebook (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations: Southeast Regional Hearing (Box 4, Folder 11)
- National Agreement: Work Plans (Box 4, Folder 12)
- The Kaiser Permanente Labor Management Partnership (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Agreements (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Case Studies (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Misc. (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Agreement Between Kaiser Permanente and Local 535 SEIU (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Labor Management Partnership Vision (Box 4, Folder 18)
- National Agreement, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 19)